So, should I start it?
No, first you start it, then you
add the load, yeah.
Because the system is twenty-four
volts, you start it from twelve,
and when it ramps up ...
Alright, Artur, I 'm recording this
for you.
Here, take a look.
I swear, I promise you, there 's
nothing here.
Here, he 's lifting it.
Here, one wire, the left wireŃthat
's the load. Arkash, show it.
Yeah, that 's the load, it 's going
to the bulb over there. Alright,
let 's remove it now.
There, on the bulb.
Everything 's fine.
And the second wireŃ
it 's ...
Show it, Arkasha.
And the second cableŃ that 's the
ground.
The second cableŃ
That 's the ground, the cable
Arkadiy is holding.
There you go.
And this is the load. This is the
load.
The little wire. Two wires come out
of it.
There you go. Alright, Arkadiy, go
ahead and connect it now.
Connect it.
It 's started.
The load is on.
Alright, that 's it, the load lit
up.
I 'm moving away from here, it 's
reflecting on me. Okay, the battery
is being disconnected.
That 's it, the setup is running in
self-power mode.
The load is oneŃone hundred fifty
kilowatts.
The load is one hundred fifty
Well, this wire right here, here it
is.
There 's nothing else here.
Film it later.
Here it is. Here Ő s the setup,
nothing ...
Arkady, can you lift it right now,
in this state?
Is it okay to lift it?
Go on, lift it, do n't be afraid.
Mainly,
the loads
don Ő t mess with them, so you don
Ő t get shocked.
Look, there Ő s nothing in there
except eggs.
These ones are already irradiated.
So, I Ő ve walked all the way
around it from every side.
Hey, my camera takes really good
pictures.
You can use it to shoot video.
Alright, Arkady, you came here as
an expertŃwhat do you think?
Well, I Ő d say I see that the
system works, and it works just as
advertised.
I mean, at least I didn Ő t see any
extra power sources.
Well, except for the cable that
goes into the ground. That Ő s it.
But that Ő s not ...
Yeah, I meanŃ
Well, we can follow the cable and
check it out.
This is our Vitaly, the one we call
Tiger.
What do you think? Did they send
you here as an expert?
So what? Everything works perfectly.
There Ő s no trick anywhere, no
deception, nothing like that?
No.
We can follow the grounding cable.
All of us here, at least, haven Ő t
seen anything suspicious.
Alright, let Ő s follow the cable
so everyone can see for themselves. A properŃ
Make a proper video.
We Ő ll make a proper video later.
Here it is, tied to the bolt, here
Ő s the black cable, right here.
Look, careful.
That Ő s it.
Are you sure that Ő s ground, you Ő
re not getting any more sparks? WellŃ
That Ő s it, here Ő s the ground.
I don Ő t see anything else here,
really.
There you go.
I would Ő ve made a ring.
We Ő re back.
We came back and checked that this
cable is just ground, nothing else.
This cable is the load, we Ő ve
confirmed it.
Alright, turn it off.
Go ahead, press it.
Arkady, press it.
That Ő s it.
Everything Ő s off.
Press start and battery launch
again.
The battery.
Start, stop.
Load.
Alright, check the paths.
I think you need to start it up.
Just turn off the load first.
The contacts are labeled over there.
You didn Ő t mix up the negative,
did you?
Red is positive. Yeah, yeah, that Ő
s right. Alright, alright, alright.
Now the load.
Should we take off the attachment?